dwbooster.com 2016-02-09

# Privacy Policy

This site is owned and operated by DWBoosters, Inc . We want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

In general, we will ask you when we need information that allows us to contact you, example: when purchasing, registering in the affiliate system or requesting technical support. The amount of personal information you are required to supply will normally be limited to that which is necessary to supply the service or carry out the transaction that you have requested.

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site.

The personal information we collect from you will be used by us to provide the service or carry out the transaction you have requested or authorized. We do not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Your personal information is never given to a third party. Your web site will not be used as reference for other customers.

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or by the anti-fraud/anti-money laundering services from the payment gateway.

Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers.

Do not hesitate to contact us if you have further questions.
